# question_data = [
# {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;Metal Gear Solid 2&quot;, you will see through the eyes of Psycho Mantis if you go first person during his boss fight.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]